Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Letter from Chief of Engineers, US Army, 1924-02-07 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Letter from Commissioners, 1906-1910 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Letter from Secretary of the Army, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Letter from Secretary of War, 1898-1914 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Reports - Anacostia Citizens' Association, 1908-05-22 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Reports - Lands and Waters of the Anacostia River, 1911-02-22 (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Reports - Protecting Interest, 1911-06-26 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Reports - Reclamation, 1898-1912 (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Rivers - Anacostia River - Reports - Road Along Anacostia River, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Potomac River, 1893-1970 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "A Guide to the Potomac River, Chesapeake Bay and James River, and an Ocean Voyage to Northern Ports", 1881 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "A Little Cruise Through Historic Waters" (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Approaching Washington by Tidewater Potomac" by Paul Wilstach, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Boats and Shipping, 1846-1957 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Boats and Shipping - Potomac River Small Craft Chart, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Early Days Along the Potomac: A History of George Washington's River Farm" by Evelyn Martha Emig, 1916-10 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Early Days on the Potomac" by Edwin Fulton Rorebeck, 1905-01 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  in the searchlight
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Great Falls of the Potomac, The" by Gilbert Grosvenor, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  in national geographic
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Great Falls of the Potomac River of Virginia, The", 1873 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Historic Potomac, The" by William Edgar Rogers, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  in five parts, missing part 2
- Rivers - Potomac River - Letter from the Acting Secretary of War, 1886 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Message of the President of the United States, 1859 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Plants of Cleft Island, Maryland" by W. L. McAtee, ca. 1954 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Pollution, 1957-1960 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Potomac Flats Case, Washington Law Reporter, 1895-11-21 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Potomac River from Fairfax Stone to Washington" (Box 33, Folder 15)
  cutter number +F859w L344Y
- Rivers - Potomac River - Report - Hydroelectric Energy at Great Falls, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Report - Reclamation of the Marshes of the Cities of Washington and Georgetown, 1882 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Trust That Will Control All Other Trusts, The" by John L. Mathews, 1909-05 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  from Hampton's Magazine, Pages 201-214
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Water Power at the Great Falls and Town of Potomac, The", 1854 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  booklet contains fold out maps
- Rivers - Potomac River - "Water Power at the Great Falls of the Potomac, The" by M. C. Ewing, 1839 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Rivers - Potomac River - Water Rights on the Potomac, 1886 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Schools - "A History of the Little 'Onpleasantness' in the Public Schools of Washington, DC" - "A History of the Little 'Onpleasantness' in the Public Schools of Washington, DC", 1871 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  First annual Report of the Superintendent of Public Schools - incomplete
- Schools - "A Remembrance: A Token of Love and Duty to the Memory of Those Gone on Before" - "A Remembrance: A Token of Love and Duty to the Memory of Those Gone on Before", 1902 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Schools - Academy of the Visitation - Academy of the Visitation, 1904 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  cutter number: +IV Ac2 1903/04
- Schools - American Institution, City of Washington - American Institution, City of Washington, 1828 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  from American Journal of Education
- Schools - An Act to Provide for the Public Instruction of Youth in Primary Schools Throughout the County of Washington in the District of Columbia - An Act to Provide for the Public Instruction of Youth in Primary Schools Throughout the County of Washington in the District of Columbia, 1862-05-20 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Schools - Arts and Crafts School - Arts and Crafts School, 1908-1910 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Schools - Ballou, Frank W. - Ballou, Frank W., 1940-12 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Schools - Belcourt Seminary School - Belcourt Seminary School, 1911-1942 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Schools - Benjamin J. Henley, Jr. Memorial Lecture - Benjamin J. Henley, Jr. Memorial Lecture, 1994-11-14 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Schools - Board of Education - Board of Education, 1972-1982 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Schools - Board of Education - Outline of Work, Home Gardening, 1906 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Schools - Bristol School for Girls - Bristol School for Girls, 1911 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Schools - Card of Censure - Card of Censure, 1874-03-13 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Schools - Central High School - Central High School, 1937-1949 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Schools - Central High School - Alumni, 1917-1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Schools - Central High School - History of Central High School, 1904-1917 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Schools - Central High School - Programs, 1917-1958 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Schools - Central High School - Report of Principal, 1911 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Schools - Chevy Chase Country Day School - Chevy Chase Country Day School, 1926-1940 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Schools - Colonial School for Girls, The - Colonial School for Girls, The, 1915-1926 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Schools - Columbia Junior College - Columbia Junior College, 1933-1938 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Schools - Columbia Junior College - Columbia Junior College, 1939-1941 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Schools - Common Schools - Common Schools, 1867-01-09 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Schools - Congressional Record - Congressional Record, 1920-1924 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Schools - Data Resource Book - Data Resource Book, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Schools - Devitt School, The - Devitt School, The, 1923-1929 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Schools - Devitt School, The - Devitt School, The, 1935-1938 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Schools - Devitt School, The - Devitt School, The, 1941-1949 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Schools - Directory of Public Schools - Directory of Public Schools, 1909-11-15 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Schools - Discipline of Teachers for 'Heresies' in the Washington (DC) Public Schools" - Discipline of Teachers for 'Heresies' in the Washington (DC) Public Schools", 1919 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Schools - District Education Newsletter - District Education Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Schools - Dunbar High School - Dunbar High School, 1976-06 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Schools - Early Schools of the District of Columbia - Early Schools of the District of Columbia (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Schools - Eastern High School - Eastern High School, 1938-2000 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Schools - Eastman School, The - Eastman School, The, 1911-1914 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Schools - Eastman School, The - Eastman School, The, 1920-1924 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Schools - Eastman School, The - Eastman School, The, 1925-1928 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Schools - Eastman School, The - Eastman School, The, 1930-1955 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Schools - Field School, The - Field School, The, ca. 1980 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Schools - Hamilton Institute - Hamilton Institute, 1906 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Schools - High Schools of the District of Columbia - High Schools of the District of Columbia, 1913-12-16 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Schools - History of the High School for Negroes in Washington - History of the High School for Negroes in Washington, 1917-07-03 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Schools - Integration - Integration, 1954-1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Schools - Intelligence and Achievement of Colored Pupils in the Public Schools of the District of Columbia - Intelligence and Achievement of Colored Pupils in the Public Schools of the District of Columbia, 1948-07 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  photocopy
- Schools - Junior High School Teachers' Association Bulletin - Junior High School Teachers' Association Bulletin, 1926-1931 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Schools - Lab School of the Kingsbury Center, The - Lab School of the Kingsbury Center, The, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Schools - Legislation - School Buildings - Legislation - School Buildings, 1878-1929 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Schools - Lewis Hotel Training School - Lewis Hotel Training School, 1922-1963 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Schools - M Street School - High School Journal, The, 1903-12 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Schools - M Street School - "M Street High School, The, 1891-1916" by Henry S. Robinson, 1980-01-19 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Schools - Maret School - Maret School, 1920-1929 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Schools - Maret School - Maret School, 1931-1939 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Schools - Maret School - Maret School, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Schools - Marjorie Webster Junior College - Marjorie Webster Junior College, 1944-1948 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Schools - Marjorie Webster Junior College - Marjorie Webster Junior College, 1950-1959 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Schools - Marjorie Webster School of Expression and Physical Education - Marjorie Webster School of Expression and Physical Education, 1929-1933 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Schools - Marjorie Webster School of Expression and Physical Education - Marjorie Webster School of Expression and Physical Education, 1935-1938 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Schools - Marjorie Webster School of Expression and Physical Education - Marjorie Webster School of Expression and Physical Education, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Schools - Mater Dei School - Mater Dei School, ca. 1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Schools - McDonogh School - McDonogh School, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Schools - McKinley Technical High School - McKinley Technical High School, 1906-1941 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Schools - Memorial of the Board of Trustees of Public Schools - Memorial of the Board of Trustees of Public Schools, 1855-02-13 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Schools - Mount Pleasant School for Secretaries - Mount Pleasant School for Secretaries, 1934-1938 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Schools - Mount Vernon Seminary for Young Ladies - Mount Vernon Seminary for Young Ladies, 1892 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Schools - National Academy of Broadcasting - National Academy of Broadcasting, ca. 1940-1958 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Schools - National Art School - National Art School (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Schools - National Trade and Professional School for Women and Girls - National Trade and Professional School for Women and Girls, ca. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Schools - Office of the Superintendant of Schools - Office of the Superintendant of Schools, 1907-01-15 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Schools - Official Handbook Public School Athletics - Official Handbook Public School Athletics, 1912-1913 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Schools - Public Schools - Public Schools, 1812-1944 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Schools - Public Schools of the District of Columbia, Textbooks and Supplies - Public Schools of the District of Columbia, Textbooks and Supplies, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Schools - Report of Committee of Schools to the Citizens' Representative Committee - Report of Committee of Schools to the Citizens' Representative Committee, 1805 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Schools - Reports - Reports, 1869-1910 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Schools - Robert H. Terrell Law School, The - Robert H. Terrell Law School, The, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Schools - Roosevelt High School - Roosevelt High School, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Schools - Saint Albans the National Cathedral School for Boys - Saint Albans the National Cathedral School for Boys, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Schools - Saint Katharine's School for Young Ladies and Girls - Saint Katharine's School for Young Ladies and Girls, 1899 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Schools - Schools of Your City, The - Schools of Your City, The, ca. 1921 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Schools - Secretarial Association of the Public Schools of the District of Columbia - Secretarial Association of the Public Schools of the District of Columbia, 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Schools - Sidwell Friends School, The - Sidwell Friends School, The, 1982-10 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Schools - Some Facts in Reguard to the School System of the District of Columbia - Some Facts in Reguard to the School System of the District of Columbia, ca. 1906 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Schools - Statement of William Guinand to the Board of Trustees of the Public Schools of Washington, DC - Statement of William Guinand to the Board of Trustees of the Public Schools of Washington, DC, 1873 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Schools - Teacher Strike - Teacher Strike, 1972-09-19 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Schools - Teachers Manual - Teachers Manual, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Schools - Teacher's Pensions - Teacher's Pensions, 1908-1919 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Schools - Temple Secretarial School - Temple Secretarial School, 1933-1968 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Schools - Theatre Arts School - Theatre Arts School, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Schools - Triumvirs of 4 1/2 Street - Triumvirs of 4 1/2 Street, 1881 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Schools - Tutoring Program - Friendship House - Tutoring Program - Friendship House, 1965-01-15 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Schools - Washington Academy of Sciences - Washington Academy of Sciences, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Schools - Washington Country School, The - Washington Country School, The, 1936-1939 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Schools - Washington High School - Washington High School, 1930-1936 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Schools - Washington High School - Cadet Corps, 1953-1956 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Schools - Washington High School - Catalogue of the Teachers and Pupils in the Washington High School, 1884-11 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Schools - Washington High School - The Review, 1886-1887 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Schools - Washington Musical Institute - Washington Musical Institute, ca. 1940 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Schools - Western High School - Western High School, 1906-1940 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Schools - Western High School - In Commemoration of the Fiftieth Anniversary of the Founding of the Western High School, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Amateur Theatre Group - Amateur Theatre Group, ca. 1949 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - American Civil Liberties Union - American Civil Liberties Union, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - American Statistical Association - American Statistical Association, 1926-01-08 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - American University Park Citizens' Association - American University Park Citizens' Association, 1931-1990 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Americus Club - Americus Club, 1874 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Appraisal Institute - Appraisal Institute, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Arkansas Avenue Community Association - Arkansas Avenue Community Association, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Argo Literary Club - Argo Literary Club, 1885-01-28 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Army League of the United States - Army League of the United States, 1913-04 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Art Students' League, The - Art Students' League, The, 1888-1898 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Association for the Preservation and Presentation of the Arts - Association for the Preservation and Presentation of the Arts, 1979-10-21 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Association of German American Societies of Greater Washington, The - Association of German American Societies of Greater Washington, The, 1976-06-06 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - At-Home Club - At-Home Club, 1883-01-10 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Audubon Society of the District of Columbia - Audubon Society of the District of Columbia, 1951-1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Biosophical Institute - Biosophical Institute, 1944-1952 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Biosophical Institute - Biosophical Institute, 1895 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Capital Review Club, The - Capital Review Club, The, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Catholic Historical Society of Washington - Catholic Historical Society of Washington, 1994-03 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chamber of Commerce - Chamber of Commerce, 1911-1934 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chamber of Commerce - Industrial Exposition, 1926-03 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America, 1942-03-21 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chevy Chase Citizens Association - Chevy Chase Citizens Association, 1928-1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chevy Chase Community Council - Chevy Chase Community Council, 1947-09 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chevy Chase, DC, Garden Club, The - Chevy Chase, DC, Garden Club, The, 1936-1939 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chevy Chase, DC, Garden Club, The - Chevy Chase, DC, Garden Club, The, 1940-1946 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chevy Chase, DC, Garden Club, The - Chevy Chase, DC, Garden Club, The, 1948-1961 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Chinese Students and Alumni Association - Chinese Students and Alumni Association, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Choral Society of Washington DC - Choral Society of Washington DC, 1907-1909 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Choral Arts Society of Washington, The - Choral Arts Society of Washington, The, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Church Home Society - Church Home Society, 1859 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Citizens' and Civic Associations - Citizens' and Civic Associations, ca. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Citizens Association of Georgetown - Citizens Association of Georgetown, 1964-1970 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Citizens' Representative Committee of One Hundred - Citizens' Representative Committee of One Hundred, 1887 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Collectors Club of Washington, The - Collectors Club of Washington, The, 1941-04 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - College Women's Club of Washington, The - College Women's Club of Washington, The, 1913-12 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Columbia Heights Citizens Association - Columbia Heights Citizens Association, 1929-1948 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Columbia Historical Society - Columbia Historical Society, 1899 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Columbia Lodge - Columbia Lodge, 1904 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Commercial Club, The - Commercial Club, The, 1911-1919 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Community Chest - Chest-O-Grams - Community Chest - Chest-O-Grams, 1929-1930 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Community Chest - Community Chest News - Community Chest - Community Chest News, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Community Chest - Directories - Community Chest - Directories, 1942-1947 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Conduit Road Citizens' Association - Conduit Road Citizens' Association, 1928-1934 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Connecticut Avenue Citizens Association - Connecticut Avenue Citizens Association, 1941-1962 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Connecticut Avenue Citizens Association - Connecticut Avenue Citizens Association, 1939-1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Connecticut Avenue Citizens Association - Newsletters, 1952-1956 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Coordinating Committee for the Enforcement of the District of Columbia Anti-Discrimination Laws - Coordinating Committee for the Enforcement of the District of Columbia Anti-Discrimination Laws, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Cosmos Club, 1983-2002 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Bulletin, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Cosmos Club - Journal of the Cosmos Club, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Daughters of the American Revolution - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1964-02-22 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Directories - Circle of Friends, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Directories - Metropolitan Washington Organization Directory, 1967-02 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Directories - Metropolitan Washington Organization Directory, 1963-11 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Directories - Metropolitan Washington Organization Directory, 1965-02 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Directories - Preservation Organizations in Washington, DC, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - District of Columbia Citizens for Better Public Education - District of Columbia Citizens for Better Public Education, 1965-1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - District of Columbia Citizens for Better Public Education - District of Columbia Citizens for Better Public Education, 1970-1981 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - District of Columbia Coalition for Youth - District of Columbia Coalition for Youth, 1982-01 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - District of Columbia Pharmaceutical Association - District of Columbia Pharmaceutical Association, 1940-1943 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - District of Columbia Sociological Society - District of Columbia Sociological Society, 1975-10 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - District of Columbia Youth Orchestra - District of Columbia Youth Orchestra, 1975-08-01 (Box 42, Folder 10)